{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:33..933.off100.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080442122","data":{"timestamp":" 947080442122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" bc4b23ba-b3e6-4e27-b50c-163a7ba23e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080454190","data":{"timestamp":" 947080454189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080455925","data":{"timestamp":" 947080455924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080457632","data":{"timestamp":" 947080457631"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080460878","data":{"timestamp":" 947080460878"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080462613","data":{"timestamp":" 947080462613"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080463509","data":{"timestamp":" 947080463508"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080463529","data":{"timestamp":" 947080463527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080465312","data":{"timestamp":" 947080465311"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080467998","data":{"timestamp":" 947080467998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080468121","data":{"timestamp":" 947080468121"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080468273","data":{"timestamp":" 947080468273"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080482871","data":{"timestamp":" 947080482871"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080489266","data":{"timestamp":" 947080489266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:33..933.off100.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080497136","data":{"timestamp":" 947080497136"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_165351"," gameId":" a31f2416-1127-425f-a118-4b7e4044abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}